Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/sathish-sekar (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

NetApp

Oracle

SQL

Certifications

ITIL Foundation Certificate in ITSM ITIL Operational Support and Analysis

Honors-Awards

High Five

Sathish Sekar

Senior DevOps Engineer | AWS | GCP | CKA | Linux Singapore

Summary

DevOps engineer having more than 9+ years of experience. I strive to keep my skills up-to-date and good at solving problems at work. I also carry the Certified kubernetes Administrator, Docker certified associate, Azure and number of AWS certifications.

Experience

Circles.Life

Senior DevOps Engineer

June 2019 - Present (1 year 10 months)

Singapore

I work for the DevOps team managing Circles.life infrastructure across Singapore, Taiwan and Australia regions.

Work On:

AWS

GCP

Kubernetes

Ansible

MySQL / MongoDB / Redis

Bash / Python Scripting

Ubuntu

Cloudflare

Bind DNS

Adobe

5 years 10 months

Senior Devops Engineer

September 2016 - June 2019 (2 years 10 months)

Bengaluru Area, India

I was part of web content management DevOps team managing www.adobe.com, helpx.adobe.com and few other customer facing websites. Responsible for architecture, Infra management and incident resolution.

Worked on:

Akamai

AWS

Centos

Python/Bash Scripting

Ansible/Chef

Icinga/Grafana

Docker / K8

Rundeck

Devops Engineer September 2013 - August 2016 (3 years)

Bengaluru Area, India

Oracle

System Administrator
June 2012 - August 2013 (1 year 3 months)

Bengaluru Area, India

Worked as Linux and NetApp Storage Administrator in the Oracle Cloud datacenter operations team.

Cognizant Technology Solutions Senior Systems Executive May 2010 - June 2012 (2 years 2 months)

Chennai Area, India

Worked as Linux and NetApp Storage Administrator for banking and Retail clients

Education

Velammal Engineering college

B.E, Electronics and Instrumentation · (2005 - 2009)